<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>Young Gyu's Blog</title>
        <link></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Young Gyu's blog]]></description>
        <atom:link href="/rss.xml" rel="self"
                   type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 15:50:43 UT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
    <title>Today, food travels thousands of miles from farms to consumers. Why does this happen?</title>
    <link>/posts/2016/06/02/ielts_writing_food_travels.html</link>
    <description><![CDATA[
<div class="hugo-blog__posts mdl-grid">
    <div class="mdl-card mdl-shadow--4dp mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
        
        <div class="mdl-card__media mdl-color-text--grey-50" style="background-image: url('/images/default.jpg'); background-color:#263238;">
            <h3>Today, food travels thousands of miles from farms to consumers. Why does this happen?</h3>
        </div>
          
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text meta">
            <div class="minilogo" style="background-image: url('/images/avatar-64x64.png');"></div>
            <div>
                <strong>Jeremy Atkinson</strong>
                <span>2016-06-01</span>
            </div>
            
            <div class="section-spacer"></div>
            
        </div>
            
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text">
            <p>Is this a positive or negative trend?</p>
<p>Nowadays, most of food we eat everyday is comming from thousands miles away even though some identical local food is available for purchasing. In this essay, I will dwell on why it is consistent and examine what impact it brought to our lives.</p>
<p>First of all, technological advances in food transportation along with cheap oil price have allowed food industry to move greater quantities of food faster and over longer distances than ever before. More specifically, air transportation, high-speed rails and a cold-storage car are the ones which enable food to travel such a long distance. In addition to this, the high demand for food in a such densely populated city is a driving force to precipitate these technological development because locally grown food cannot meet such a high demand. Accordingly, it is inevitable to use those technological advancement to unravel the food shortage problem in such densely populated cities.</p>
<p>It is clear that this change has brought many negative effects to our lives in many respects. One ot the most detrimental effects is that most of food relying on long journey have to be processed with much toxic checmical to preserve the freshness of the products or prevent the food from decay. Such process will also cause many unexpected problems such as diseases caused by intake of the food, additional environmental contamination from the checmical process of the food. Additionally, the transportation of the food will also contribute to the aggravating global warming issue, since the food need to be delivered from the place it grow to a city in which most of consumer live.</p>
<p>In summary, the two most important factors, which are technological advances and food shortage in a densely populated city, are the main contributors to make this trend feasible. In my opinion, such trend seems to have many adverse effects and thus it is desirable to encourage people to consume more locally grown food and curtail the increasing population in a city.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="mdl-color-text--primary-contrast mdl-card__supporting-text comments"> 
            
            <p>Tags: <a href="/tags/ielts.html">ielts</a>, <a href="/tags/writing.html">writing</a>, <a href="/tags/food.html">food</a>, <a href="/tags/travels.html">travels</a></p>
            <p>Category: <a href="/categories/02.html">02</a></p>
        </div>  
    </div>

    <nav class="hugo-nav mdl-color-text--grey-50 mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
    
        <a href="/post/shellprocesses/" class="hugo-nav__button">
            <button class="mdl-button mdl-js-button mdl-js-ripple-effect mdl-button--icon mdl-color--white mdl-color-text--grey-900" role="presentation" data-upgraded=",MaterialButton,MaterialRipple">
            <i class="icon ion-android-arrow-back"></i>
            <span class="mdl-button__ripple-container"><span class="mdl-ripple"></span></span></button>
            Older
        </a>
        <div class="section-spacer"></div>
    
    </nav>

</div>]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 15:50:43 UT</pubDate>
    <guid>/posts/2016/06/02/ielts_writing_food_travels.html</guid>
    <dc:creator>Young Gyu Park</dc:creator>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Traffic jams are a problem in many towns and cities. Some people suggest that governments should build wider roads in order to solve the problem</title>
    <link>/posts/2016/06/01/ielts_writing_traffic_jams.html</link>
    <description><![CDATA[
<div class="hugo-blog__posts mdl-grid">
    <div class="mdl-card mdl-shadow--4dp mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
        
        <div class="mdl-card__media mdl-color-text--grey-50" style="background-image: url('/images/default.jpg'); background-color:#263238;">
            <h3>Traffic jams are a problem in many towns and cities. Some people suggest that governments should build wider roads in order to solve the problem</h3>
        </div>
          
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text meta">
            <div class="minilogo" style="background-image: url('/images/avatar-64x64.png');"></div>
            <div>
                <strong>Jeremy Atkinson</strong>
                <span>2016-05-31</span>
            </div>
            
            <div class="section-spacer"></div>
            
        </div>
            
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text">
            <p>Do you agree or disagree?</p>
<p>Aggravating traffic congestion is a major concern to many cities. Many people suggest different solutions for the problem. One of the solutions that is commonly debated is that governments should take a policy to construct wider roads which will target to increase the capacities of the roads to contain more cars. However, I firmly object the idea since the manner cannot be the ultimate solution for the problem.</p>
<p>To begin with, it is not a very desirable idea to build a wider road since it will hamper the vitality of the city in various ways. More specifically, the policy to build a wider road will not make a city more livable as a city more focused on development for the convenience of the driver will not be a place where many people want to live. For example, there is a newly built city with 10 lanes of road in Brazil because they want to build a city which free from the common traffic jams problem. However, they sooner or later encounter another problem that nobody want to live the city because the city is only considering traffic issue by building a wide road.</p>
<p>Secondly, the effort to build a wider road will create more incentives for people to buy more cars, which exacerbate the traffic congestion again. It is ironic that the solution to lessen traffic congestion is actually contributing to make the problem worsen. For instance, about ten years ago, a mayor in my city announced a very robust plan to build wider roads to reslove the worsening traffic jams. However, the plan seems to be effective temporary but the convenience the plan brought palyed a role as an incentive to attract more people to buying cars.</p>
<p>In conclusion, I absolutely agree with the idea that governments should not abandon any policies to extend the road to alleviate the deteriorating traffic problem. Therefore, governments need to come up with idea as to how to reduce the number of cars instead of widening roads.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="mdl-color-text--primary-contrast mdl-card__supporting-text comments"> 
            
            <p>Tags: <a href="/tags/ielts.html">ielts</a>, <a href="/tags/writing.html">writing</a>, <a href="/tags/traffic%20jams.html">traffic jams</a></p>
            <p>Category: <a href="/categories/01.html">01</a></p>
        </div>  
    </div>

    <nav class="hugo-nav mdl-color-text--grey-50 mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
    
        <a href="/post/shellprocesses/" class="hugo-nav__button">
            <button class="mdl-button mdl-js-button mdl-js-ripple-effect mdl-button--icon mdl-color--white mdl-color-text--grey-900" role="presentation" data-upgraded=",MaterialButton,MaterialRipple">
            <i class="icon ion-android-arrow-back"></i>
            <span class="mdl-button__ripple-container"><span class="mdl-ripple"></span></span></button>
            Older
        </a>
        <div class="section-spacer"></div>
    
    </nav>

</div>]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 16:42:36 UT</pubDate>
    <guid>/posts/2016/06/01/ielts_writing_traffic_jams.html</guid>
    <dc:creator>Young Gyu Park</dc:creator>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Some working parents believe that child-care centers provide the best care for their children. However, others think family members, such as grandparents, provide the best care</title>
    <link>/posts/2016/05/31/ielts_writing_child_care.html</link>
    <description><![CDATA[
<div class="hugo-blog__posts mdl-grid">
    <div class="mdl-card mdl-shadow--4dp mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
        
        <div class="mdl-card__media mdl-color-text--grey-50" style="background-image: url('/images/default.jpg'); background-color:#263238;">
            <h3>Some working parents believe that child-care centers provide the best care for their children. However, others think family members, such as grandparents, provide the best care</h3>
        </div>
          
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text meta">
            <div class="minilogo" style="background-image: url('/images/avatar-64x64.png');"></div>
            <div>
                <strong>Jeremy Atkinson</strong>
                <span>2016-05-30</span>
            </div>
            
            <div class="section-spacer"></div>
            
        </div>
            
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text">
            <p>Discuss both views and give your own opinion.</p>
<p>It is quite controversial that childcare facilities will be the best place for children to be well taken care of, since other people believe that family members should be in charge of raising kids. In this essay, I will examine the two condradicting views and add my thought on the subject.</p>
<p>To begin with, it is no doubt that child-care facilities are more competent in comparison of child’s relatives in terms of taking care of children. This is because people who are working in the child-care centers are required to be trained and educated in a university or special education centers for childcare, which ehnace their speciality in childcare. In addition to this, most of child-care facilities are well designed and specialized to serve the purpose of nurturing kids, which is believed to be lacking in family home.</p>
<p>On the other hand, the most evident advantage we can gain from relatives involvement of nurturing children is that they can take care of kids with affection and interest. However, it is hard to find such strong affection and interest in child-care centers as people in the centers usually do not have any emotional connection with the kids they are raising. Another benefit from raising kids with the help of family members is that we can nurture children in the most comfortable environment, which is abosultely conducive to ensure a sense of security.</p>
<p>To sum up, the two differen point of views with regard to raising kids by family members or child-care centers seem to have their own advantages and disadvantages. In my opinion, raising kids with family members seems to provide the best environment for the kids in various aspects.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="mdl-color-text--primary-contrast mdl-card__supporting-text comments"> 
            
            <p>Tags: <a href="/tags/ielts.html">ielts</a>, <a href="/tags/writing.html">writing</a>, <a href="/tags/child-care.html">child-care</a></p>
            <p>Category: <a href="/categories/31.html">31</a></p>
        </div>  
    </div>

    <nav class="hugo-nav mdl-color-text--grey-50 mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
    
        <a href="/post/shellprocesses/" class="hugo-nav__button">
            <button class="mdl-button mdl-js-button mdl-js-ripple-effect mdl-button--icon mdl-color--white mdl-color-text--grey-900" role="presentation" data-upgraded=",MaterialButton,MaterialRipple">
            <i class="icon ion-android-arrow-back"></i>
            <span class="mdl-button__ripple-container"><span class="mdl-ripple"></span></span></button>
            Older
        </a>
        <div class="section-spacer"></div>
    
    </nav>

</div>]]></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 16:20:08 UT</pubDate>
    <guid>/posts/2016/05/31/ielts_writing_child_care.html</guid>
    <dc:creator>Young Gyu Park</dc:creator>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Nowadays, people have unhealthy diets and do not do enough exercise</title>
    <link>/posts/2016/05/30/ielts_writing_unhealthy_diets_exercise.html</link>
    <description><![CDATA[
<div class="hugo-blog__posts mdl-grid">
    <div class="mdl-card mdl-shadow--4dp mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
        
        <div class="mdl-card__media mdl-color-text--grey-50" style="background-image: url('/images/default.jpg'); background-color:#263238;">
            <h3>Nowadays, people have unhealthy diets and do not do enough exercise</h3>
        </div>
          
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text meta">
            <div class="minilogo" style="background-image: url('/images/avatar-64x64.png');"></div>
            <div>
                <strong>Jeremy Atkinson</strong>
                <span>2016-05-29</span>
            </div>
            
            <div class="section-spacer"></div>
            
        </div>
            
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text">
            <p>Discuss the reasons for this and make suggestions on how to encourage people to have healthy lifestyles.</p>
<p>It is a grave concern in most societies that people are experiencing many health problems caused by instant food and lack of exercise. In this essay, I will analyze the reasons why this problems are persistent and probe what other solutions we can adopt to rein the increasing trend.</p>
<p>First of all, the most evident reason of encouraging people to have unhealthy food and discouraging people to have less exercise is people’s overloaded work. As the competition among people is severe, people hesitate to spend enough time to prepare a food and to exercise in gym. This is because they believe that the saved time from cooking food and not exercising can direct at enhancing their competitiveness in various aspects in a soceity. Thus their reckless and frequent intake of instant food and negligence in exercise resulted in the current health problem.</p>
<p>Accordingly, the most imminent task to mitigate the aggravating health issue among people is to lessen people’ work load, which will give some time to review themselves in terms of health. Furthermore, a community’s collective effort to curtail the accelerating competition in our soceity is also beneficial to minimize the worsening consequence of people’s health. Hence, soceity as a whole need to find out a way to reduce the level of competition and provide a specific policy to extricate people from their busy work.</p>
<p>In conclusion, the health probem seem to lie in the social structure to evoke more competition trying to exract more outcome from the employees, which endanger people’s health. Therefore, it is crucial to eradicate</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="mdl-color-text--primary-contrast mdl-card__supporting-text comments"> 
            
            <p>Tags: <a href="/tags/ielts.html">ielts</a>, <a href="/tags/writing.html">writing</a>, <a href="/tags/unhealthy.html">unhealthy</a>, <a href="/tags/diets.html">diets</a>, <a href="/tags/exercise.html">exercise</a></p>
            <p>Category: <a href="/categories/30.html">30</a></p>
        </div>  
    </div>

    <nav class="hugo-nav mdl-color-text--grey-50 mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
    
        <a href="/post/shellprocesses/" class="hugo-nav__button">
            <button class="mdl-button mdl-js-button mdl-js-ripple-effect mdl-button--icon mdl-color--white mdl-color-text--grey-900" role="presentation" data-upgraded=",MaterialButton,MaterialRipple">
            <i class="icon ion-android-arrow-back"></i>
            <span class="mdl-button__ripple-container"><span class="mdl-ripple"></span></span></button>
            Older
        </a>
        <div class="section-spacer"></div>
    
    </nav>

</div>]]></description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2016 16:07:43 UT</pubDate>
    <guid>/posts/2016/05/30/ielts_writing_unhealthy_diets_exercise.html</guid>
    <dc:creator>Young Gyu Park</dc:creator>
</item>
<item>
    <title>As well as making money, businesses also have social responsibilities.</title>
    <link>/posts/2016/05/27/ielts_writing_business_responsibilities.html</link>
    <description><![CDATA[
<div class="hugo-blog__posts mdl-grid">
    <div class="mdl-card mdl-shadow--4dp mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
        
        <div class="mdl-card__media mdl-color-text--grey-50" style="background-image: url('/images/default.jpg'); background-color:#263238;">
            <h3>As well as making money, businesses also have social responsibilities.</h3>
        </div>
          
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text meta">
            <div class="minilogo" style="background-image: url('/images/avatar-64x64.png');"></div>
            <div>
                <strong>Jeremy Atkinson</strong>
                <span>2016-05-26</span>
            </div>
            
            <div class="section-spacer"></div>
            
        </div>
            
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text">
            <p>To what extent do you agree or disagree with this statement?</p>
<p>There is no denying that business have been large part of human activity. As the influence of business is increasing, people start to contemplate and require the social responsibility of a business. In my opinion, it is absurd argument that a business is completely free from the social responsibility because it is the organization for the purpose of pursuing profit.</p>
<p>To begin with, any human activities including business should take a certain amount of social responsibility because they are inextricably interwined with other people’s lives. For instance, if a factory release contaminated water into river without taking proper measure to purify the water, it might lead to jeopardizing other people’s lives. Considering the nature of business which prioritize the profit, it seems quite natural for the owner of the business to take an action to minimize the cost, which serve well the purpose of the business while hampering the quality of other people’s lives.</p>
<p>Secondly, most of business which is reluctant to fulfill their social responsibility seems to end up with the failure of the business because it will lose the customers’ trust. For example, the most prestigious company in my country did not faithfully conduct the rules to protect its employees from the hazardous material, which cause many employees’ lives. As a result, they cannot help but lose very large portion of market share due to the incident which lead to campaign against , which might result in the bankruptcy of the business.</p>
<p>In conclusion, it is necessarily not only for the success of a business but the community we live that any businesses pursuing profit should abide by the principles to serve social responsibilities. Therefore, we need to encourage businesses people to participate this movement to make our societies a better place by asking them to respect social responsibilities.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="mdl-color-text--primary-contrast mdl-card__supporting-text comments"> 
            
            <p>Tags: <a href="/tags/ielts.html">ielts</a>, <a href="/tags/writing.html">writing</a>, <a href="/tags/business.html">business</a>, <a href="/tags/responsibilities.html">responsibilities</a></p>
            <p>Category: <a href="/categories/27.html">27</a></p>
        </div>  
    </div>

    <nav class="hugo-nav mdl-color-text--grey-50 mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
    
        <a href="/post/shellprocesses/" class="hugo-nav__button">
            <button class="mdl-button mdl-js-button mdl-js-ripple-effect mdl-button--icon mdl-color--white mdl-color-text--grey-900" role="presentation" data-upgraded=",MaterialButton,MaterialRipple">
            <i class="icon ion-android-arrow-back"></i>
            <span class="mdl-button__ripple-container"><span class="mdl-ripple"></span></span></button>
            Older
        </a>
        <div class="section-spacer"></div>
    
    </nav>

</div>]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2016 16:12:31 UT</pubDate>
    <guid>/posts/2016/05/27/ielts_writing_business_responsibilities.html</guid>
    <dc:creator>Young Gyu Park</dc:creator>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Some people think news have no connection to people's lives, so it is a waste of time to read the news in the newspaper and watch television news programs.</title>
    <link>/posts/2016/05/26/ielts_writing_news_television_programs.html</link>
    <description><![CDATA[
<div class="hugo-blog__posts mdl-grid">
    <div class="mdl-card mdl-shadow--4dp mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
        
        <div class="mdl-card__media mdl-color-text--grey-50" style="background-image: url('/images/default.jpg'); background-color:#263238;">
            <h3>Some people think news have no connection to people's lives, so it is a waste of time to read the news in the newspaper and watch television news programs.</h3>
        </div>
          
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text meta">
            <div class="minilogo" style="background-image: url('/images/avatar-64x64.png');"></div>
            <div>
                <strong>Jeremy Atkinson</strong>
                <span>2016-05-25</span>
            </div>
            
            <div class="section-spacer"></div>
            
        </div>
            
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text">
            <p>To what extent do you agree or disagree with this statement?</p>
<p>Some people criticize that reading a newspaper or watching television is completely a waste of time, since they believe that news generated by media are quite far from the human life. In my opinion, it is still worthwhile to pay attention to the newspaper and television news programs because the information people obtain from those media still in relation to human activities.</p>
<p>First of all, it is almost inconceivable that newspaper and news programs on television are not interested in people’s lives. This is because people’s lives are the most interesting news that most of people are inclined to know. If the media fails to meet the people’s interest or expectation, they will be highly likely to lead to the failure of their businesses. It is inevitable that people will not purchase the newspaper and watch the news programs only dealing with the issues which have nothing to do with human life.</p>
<p>Secondly, it is well known fact that the key role of the media is to deliver the news that are introducing people’s lives to the public. If the media companies do not properly conduct their fundamental role, it is actually undermining the ground of their existences. For example, if there are media companies which do not make an effort to publicize human activities such as protests, politics and business, the companies will naturally encounter severe public outcry for the negligence of their duties.</p>
<p>In summary, nobody cannot deny the fact that most of news are inextricably interwined with human lives. Therefore, the media companies need to fulfill their basic role as well as pay more attention to human life, which result in the success of their businesses.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="mdl-color-text--primary-contrast mdl-card__supporting-text comments"> 
            
            <p>Tags: <a href="/tags/ielts.html">ielts</a>, <a href="/tags/writing.html">writing</a>, <a href="/tags/news.html">news</a>, <a href="/tags/television.html">television</a></p>
            <p>Category: <a href="/categories/26.html">26</a></p>
        </div>  
    </div>

    <nav class="hugo-nav mdl-color-text--grey-50 mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
    
        <a href="/post/shellprocesses/" class="hugo-nav__button">
            <button class="mdl-button mdl-js-button mdl-js-ripple-effect mdl-button--icon mdl-color--white mdl-color-text--grey-900" role="presentation" data-upgraded=",MaterialButton,MaterialRipple">
            <i class="icon ion-android-arrow-back"></i>
            <span class="mdl-button__ripple-container"><span class="mdl-ripple"></span></span></button>
            Older
        </a>
        <div class="section-spacer"></div>
    
    </nav>

</div>]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2016 20:05:36 UT</pubDate>
    <guid>/posts/2016/05/26/ielts_writing_news_television_programs.html</guid>
    <dc:creator>Young Gyu Park</dc:creator>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Many goverments think that economic progress is their most important goal. Some people, however, think that other types of progress are equally important for a country</title>
    <link>/posts/2016/05/25/ielts_writing_economic_progress.html</link>
    <description><![CDATA[
<div class="hugo-blog__posts mdl-grid">
    <div class="mdl-card mdl-shadow--4dp mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
        
        <div class="mdl-card__media mdl-color-text--grey-50" style="background-image: url('/images/default.jpg'); background-color:#263238;">
            <h3>Many goverments think that economic progress is their most important goal. Some people, however, think that other types of progress are equally important for a country</h3>
        </div>
          
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text meta">
            <div class="minilogo" style="background-image: url('/images/avatar-64x64.png');"></div>
            <div>
                <strong>Jeremy Atkinson</strong>
                <span>2016-05-24</span>
            </div>
            
            <div class="section-spacer"></div>
            
        </div>
            
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text">
            <p>Discuss both these views and give your own opinion.</p>
<p>Many countries pursue economic development as their most prominent priority whereas other countries insist that there are other types of progress should take precedence over economic goal. In this essay, I will deal with these two point of views and express my thought on the issue.</p>
<p>To begin with, there is no denying that economic development should be the main priority in the governments’ goals because it is very hard to imagine that people living in poverty are happy. Basically, a country need to pursue economic progress at least to unravel people’s problems such as food, shelter and clothes. For example, people in North Korea certainly live in painful life as they can hardly find a food to eat. In addition to this, many people in North Korea also want to escape the country to find a better place to live, which result in the country hard to sustain. Thus, economic development should be the key goal for countries.</p>
<p>Despite the fact that many countries put the key priority on economic development, other countries believe that there are a variety of development should be done to enhance people’s happiness. It is no doubt that people will purse a better quality of life once they do not have any difficulty to meet their basic needs such as hunger, house and clothes. For instance, many advanced countries make a tremendous effort to make better environments where people are living. More specifically, most of economically abundant countries have been investing huge amount of money on cultural businesses to make our lives more enjoyable.</p>
<p>In conclusion, I absolutely agree with the idea that economic development should take precedence over other types of developments because people who cannot afford to buy a food will certainly live in great agony as well as be not interested in other types of developments. Therefore, countries should not treat the economic development equally with other types of developments.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="mdl-color-text--primary-contrast mdl-card__supporting-text comments"> 
            
            <p>Tags: <a href="/tags/ielts.html">ielts</a>, <a href="/tags/writing.html">writing</a>, <a href="/tags/economic.html">economic</a>, <a href="/tags/progress.html">progress</a></p>
            <p>Category: <a href="/categories/25.html">25</a></p>
        </div>  
    </div>

    <nav class="hugo-nav mdl-color-text--grey-50 mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
    
        <a href="/post/shellprocesses/" class="hugo-nav__button">
            <button class="mdl-button mdl-js-button mdl-js-ripple-effect mdl-button--icon mdl-color--white mdl-color-text--grey-900" role="presentation" data-upgraded=",MaterialButton,MaterialRipple">
            <i class="icon ion-android-arrow-back"></i>
            <span class="mdl-button__ripple-container"><span class="mdl-ripple"></span></span></button>
            Older
        </a>
        <div class="section-spacer"></div>
    
    </nav>

</div>]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 15:14:23 UT</pubDate>
    <guid>/posts/2016/05/25/ielts_writing_economic_progress.html</guid>
    <dc:creator>Young Gyu Park</dc:creator>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Many children are encouraged by their parents to get a part time job in their free time</title>
    <link>/posts/2016/05/20/ielts_writing_part_time_job.html</link>
    <description><![CDATA[
<div class="hugo-blog__posts mdl-grid">
    <div class="mdl-card mdl-shadow--4dp mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
        
        <div class="mdl-card__media mdl-color-text--grey-50" style="background-image: url('/images/default.jpg'); background-color:#263238;">
            <h3>Many children are encouraged by their parents to get a part time job in their free time</h3>
        </div>
          
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text meta">
            <div class="minilogo" style="background-image: url('/images/avatar-64x64.png');"></div>
            <div>
                <strong>Jeremy Atkinson</strong>
                <span>2016-05-19</span>
            </div>
            
            <div class="section-spacer"></div>
            
        </div>
            
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text">
            <p>What are the advantages and disadvantages to children of doing so?</p>
<p>Many parents believe that having a part time job during vacations for their kids is certainly conducive to their growth in many aspects. However, others insist that studying should take precedence over an experience by having a part time job, since studying can guarantee a better income in their future career. In this article, I will deal with drawbacks and benefits that I can expect from the issue.</p>
<p>To begin with, it is very evident that students who had a part time jos during their vacations are able to gain a variety of experiences. Such experiences are hardly obtained through the class, since the key of the current education system is mainly to develop students’ intellectual ability. For example, I had worked in construction site for my summer vacation in high school, At the time, I did not anticipate that this experience will be connected with my future career but when I seek to find a job in construction companies, I was an advantageous in comparison to other candidates who are lack of pre-experience</p>
<p>Despite the fact that there are many advantages in having a part time job, nobody cannot deny the fact that there are some drawbacks as well in having a part time job. First and foremost, children need to sacrifice their time to study for having a part time job, which might result in losing their competitiveness in study. For instance, my high school friend who have ranked at the top in my class have worked in game room as a part time worker for his vacation. However, he was mesmerized with the game and spent most of his time to play a computer game, which make him fail to get an admission from the university.</p>
<p>In conclusion, it is clear that students having a part time job during a vacation had negative effects as well as positive ones. What is more important is how to benefit from the positive effects while minimizing the negative ones, which is right attitude for the part time job.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="mdl-color-text--primary-contrast mdl-card__supporting-text comments"> 
            
            <p>Tags: <a href="/tags/ielts.html">ielts</a>, <a href="/tags/writing.html">writing</a>, <a href="/tags/part%20time.html">part time</a>, <a href="/tags/job.html">job</a></p>
            <p>Category: <a href="/categories/20.html">20</a></p>
        </div>  
    </div>

    <nav class="hugo-nav mdl-color-text--grey-50 mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
    
        <a href="/post/shellprocesses/" class="hugo-nav__button">
            <button class="mdl-button mdl-js-button mdl-js-ripple-effect mdl-button--icon mdl-color--white mdl-color-text--grey-900" role="presentation" data-upgraded=",MaterialButton,MaterialRipple">
            <i class="icon ion-android-arrow-back"></i>
            <span class="mdl-button__ripple-container"><span class="mdl-ripple"></span></span></button>
            Older
        </a>
        <div class="section-spacer"></div>
    
    </nav>

</div>]]></description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 16:37:59 UT</pubDate>
    <guid>/posts/2016/05/20/ielts_writing_part_time_job.html</guid>
    <dc:creator>Young Gyu Park</dc:creator>
</item>
<item>
    <title>The role of education is to prepare children for the modern world. Schools should cut art and music out of the curriculum so that children can focus on useful subjects such as information technology</title>
    <link>/posts/2016/05/19/ielts_writing_education_subjects.html</link>
    <description><![CDATA[
<div class="hugo-blog__posts mdl-grid">
    <div class="mdl-card mdl-shadow--4dp mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
        
        <div class="mdl-card__media mdl-color-text--grey-50" style="background-image: url('/images/default.jpg'); background-color:#263238;">
            <h3>The role of education is to prepare children for the modern world. Schools should cut art and music out of the curriculum so that children can focus on useful subjects such as information technology</h3>
        </div>
          
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text meta">
            <div class="minilogo" style="background-image: url('/images/avatar-64x64.png');"></div>
            <div>
                <strong>Jeremy Atkinson</strong>
                <span>2016-05-18</span>
            </div>
            
            <div class="section-spacer"></div>
            
        </div>
            
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text">
            <p>To what extent do you agree</p>
<p>The main purpose of education is to raise children for a competent individual in the rapidly changing modern world. In that process, the educational institutes are encouraged to abandon some of the subjects which are largely regarded as useless such as art and music. However, I believe that those subjects are really crucial to nurture children more mature and accountable.</p>
<p>First of all, as the influence of information technology is increasingly powerful, schools tend to value highly on the subjects which are deemed useful in the modern society while neglecting or remove music or art from the formal educational course. Such educational policy should be banned as soon as possible because those subjects prove that they are actually contributing hugely to human mental development which is quite important part of education. For example, the art class that I took in my high school leave a big impression to me, since it teach me the way to see the situation or object in different angles.</p>
<p>Secondly, nobody deny the fact that a human being is an emotional creature. In out daily lives, people are constantly affected by their emotion in a variety of manners. Accordingly, art and music which are believed to be essential subjects to develop and train human mind or emotion should gain their due recognition in education system. If we do not pay attention to foster those subjects, it is inevitable that there are majority of people, who are intellectually outstanding but lack of sympathy or emotions, in our society.</p>
<p>In conclusion, it is understandable that many people strive to find a way to make their kids more capable in competing each other. However, if we only focus on developing our children’s pratical knowledge in modern world, we might end up with a result which there are many inhuman people who are technically capable in our society.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="mdl-color-text--primary-contrast mdl-card__supporting-text comments"> 
            
            <p>Tags: <a href="/tags/ielts.html">ielts</a>, <a href="/tags/writing.html">writing</a>, <a href="/tags/education.html">education</a>, <a href="/tags/subjects.html">subjects</a></p>
            <p>Category: <a href="/categories/19.html">19</a></p>
        </div>  
    </div>

    <nav class="hugo-nav mdl-color-text--grey-50 mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
    
        <a href="/post/shellprocesses/" class="hugo-nav__button">
            <button class="mdl-button mdl-js-button mdl-js-ripple-effect mdl-button--icon mdl-color--white mdl-color-text--grey-900" role="presentation" data-upgraded=",MaterialButton,MaterialRipple">
            <i class="icon ion-android-arrow-back"></i>
            <span class="mdl-button__ripple-container"><span class="mdl-ripple"></span></span></button>
            Older
        </a>
        <div class="section-spacer"></div>
    
    </nav>

</div>]]></description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2016 20:44:54 UT</pubDate>
    <guid>/posts/2016/05/19/ielts_writing_education_subjects.html</guid>
    <dc:creator>Young Gyu Park</dc:creator>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Many museums charge for admission while others are free. Do you think the advantages of charging people for admission to museums outweigh the disadvantages?</title>
    <link>/posts/2016/05/18/ielts_writing_museum_charge.html</link>
    <description><![CDATA[
<div class="hugo-blog__posts mdl-grid">
    <div class="mdl-card mdl-shadow--4dp mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
        
        <div class="mdl-card__media mdl-color-text--grey-50" style="background-image: url('/images/default.jpg'); background-color:#263238;">
            <h3>Many museums charge for admission while others are free. Do you think the advantages of charging people for admission to museums outweigh the disadvantages?</h3>
        </div>
          
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text meta">
            <div class="minilogo" style="background-image: url('/images/avatar-64x64.png');"></div>
            <div>
                <strong>Jeremy Atkinson</strong>
                <span>2016-05-17</span>
            </div>
            
            <div class="section-spacer"></div>
            
        </div>
            
        <div class="mdl-color-text--grey-700 mdl-card__supporting-text">
            <p>Give reasons for your answer and include any relevant examples from your own knowledge or experience.</p>
<p>Museums are quite important facilities to human life in many aspects. Especially, for the purpose of education of young children, it has been playing a crucial role in our society. In order to maximize the benefits of such facilities, it is important question as to whether the museum should be operating on a charge basis or not. Personally, I stick to the thought that the cost of running museum should be compensated by the public fund, which lead to the free service of museum.</p>
<p>The one of evident benefits we can expect from the free charge of museum is that it will provide a chance to enjoy the museum to people which cannot afford to pay the fee for the admission. It goes without saying that it will contribute to narrow down the gap between rich and poor people in terms of education opportunities. For example, when I traveled Philippine, I had a chance to visit a museum. The museum charge a small fee for the entrance which is not a big money to me but local people felt that the fee is almost half of their daily income, which deprive the people of the chance to learn and experience their museum because of the fee.</p>
<p>On the other hand, there are many drawbacks in museum running on the basis of charge. Firstly, charging fee for admission in a museum could play a role of a barrier to block people having a willingness to learn something from the museum but no money for the admission. Additionally, it is shameful to discourage people to participate in learning activities in museum due to the fee. Secondly, if the charge of the service of a museum is justified, the museum is hardly becoming a place open to most of people regardless of their financial status, which might contribute to build an awareness that the museum is a closed facility and a enjoyable place for rich.</p>
<p>To sum up, it seems evident that the drawbacks of admission fee for the museum exceed the advantages. Therefore, as more people freely enjoy the museum without admission fee, the museum will become a place loved by many people, which lead to the improvement of the quality of people’s lives.</p>
        </div>
        
        <div class="mdl-color-text--primary-contrast mdl-card__supporting-text comments"> 
            
            <p>Tags: <a href="/tags/ielts.html">ielts</a>, <a href="/tags/writing.html">writing</a>, <a href="/tags/museums.html">museums</a>, <a href="/tags/charge.html">charge</a></p>
            <p>Category: <a href="/categories/18.html">18</a></p>
        </div>  
    </div>

    <nav class="hugo-nav mdl-color-text--grey-50 mdl-cell mdl-cell--12-col">
    
        <a href="/post/shellprocesses/" class="hugo-nav__button">
            <button class="mdl-button mdl-js-button mdl-js-ripple-effect mdl-button--icon mdl-color--white mdl-color-text--grey-900" role="presentation" data-upgraded=",MaterialButton,MaterialRipple">
            <i class="icon ion-android-arrow-back"></i>
            <span class="mdl-button__ripple-container"><span class="mdl-ripple"></span></span></button>
            Older
        </a>
        <div class="section-spacer"></div>
    
    </nav>

</div>]]></description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 16:02:09 UT</pubDate>
    <guid>/posts/2016/05/18/ielts_writing_museum_charge.html</guid>
    <dc:creator>Young Gyu Park</dc:creator>
</item>

    </channel>
</rss>
