<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>[Young Gyu's blog]</title>
        <description>Young Gyu Park Story, Tech and Life</description>
        <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/</link>
        <language>ko</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 12:43:47 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 12:19:52 GMT</pubDate>
        <ttl>180</ttl>
        <atom:link href="http://ygpark2.github.io/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

        
        <item>
            <title>Some people believe that unpaid community service should be a compulsory part of high school programms</title>
            <description>&lt;p id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;Some people believe that unpaid community service should be a compulsory part of high school programms (for example working for a charity, improving the neighbourhood or teaching sports to younger children) What extent do you agree or disagree?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;Some of the essential services in our community will not work properly without volunteers’ dedicated effort. I believe such volunteers have been educated about how important their works are and experienced how much pleasure they will receive in return for their work. Thus I totally agree with the idea to include the social service program to high school curriculum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;Firstly, we need to dwell on the several benefit from enforcing the course to ask the high school students to do social service.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/21/ielt_writing_unpaid_community_service.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/21/ielt_writing_unpaid_community_service.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/21/ielt_writing_unpaid_community_service.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 12:19:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Art is considered an important part of a society as well as an expressio nof its culture. Do you think it is important for children to be taught art? Do you think children should be encouraged to focus an art rather than other subjects?</title>
            <description>&lt;p id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;Art has been essential element of any human society from prehistoric times. However, at these days, the unprecedented technology development seems to undermine the value of art in human growth. I personally believe that art seems to be undervalued that is should deserve and we need to find a way to promote to the education of art in our public school.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;First of all, as the increasing importance of creativity in many areas is receiving more attention, people tend to pay more attention to how to enhance their creativity. The most effective method to develop creativity has been the education of art since we can easily find the most creative person among the artists. In addition to this, art can also be used to cure a person who are psychologically damaged. Therefore, we can expect the benefits in terms of psychological aspect as well as develping creativity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;Even though the critical importance of art has been recoginized by an increasing number of people, the recognition with regard to art in our education system seems to be out of tune with public concerns. A big portion of our time in schools has been dedicated to teach other subjects by neglecting to spend more time to teach art. Furthermore, the exam to determine their ability to study in university to not include art subject, which eventually discourage students to study art.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-4&#39;&gt;In conclusion, we are living in the society or the education system that make little account of art subject. However, we have to build up a strong art education to foster more creative person.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/18/ielt_writing_art_education.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/18/ielt_writing_art_education.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/18/ielt_writing_art_education.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2015 23:42:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Some experts believe that it is better for children to begin learning a foreign language at primary school rather than secondary school Do you think advantages of this outweigh the disadvantages?</title>
            <description>&lt;p id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;The importance of learning a foreign language is increasing, as the globalizatio nis expedited in many countries. In this trend, some language master argue that foreign language education should be taught at primary school in stead of secondary school to maximize the effectiveness of the education of language learning. However, I believe that secondary school is the best time to teach foreign language because we can expect more benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;The first advantage of teaching foreign language at secondary school is that the students can easily understand the meaning of foreign word thanks to their concrete and abundant mother tongue’s vocabulary. If you teach foreign language to a primary student who is not fully developed his or her navive language, it will be extremly hard because he or she cannot understand a new foreign word which he or she never learnt the corresponding word in his or her mother tongue. In addition to this, adding new language to their premature mother tongue will not only deter the development of their mother tongue but also be not helpful to learn a foreign language beased on their fragile mother tongue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;On contrary, if we teach a foreign language from elementary school, we can easily find many drawbacks. The first thing among them is that to teach foreign language to elementary studentswill be not only hard but not useful since it will be extremely difficult to motivate students who are still having trouble to understand their own language. Secondary, the early starting of teaching foreign language will destroy their interest as to foreign language, which will lead people to the stage of abandoning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-4&#39;&gt;To sum up, the disadvantages we expect from the teaching foreign language in elementary school seems to outweigh the advantages we can obtain from secondary school.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/18/ielt_writing_forein_langugage.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/18/ielt_writing_forein_langugage.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/18/ielt_writing_forein_langugage.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2015 22:08:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>hakyll 설치법</title>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;lessc dependencies installation&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;npm install less-plugin-clean-css npm install lodash npm install commander npm install gear npm install del npm install gear-lib&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-4&#39;&gt;새글 파일 생성&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-5&#39;&gt;./jake &#39;doc:post[파일명, 제목]&#39;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-6&#39;&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/17/hakyll_installation.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/17/hakyll_installation.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/17/hakyll_installation.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 15:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>8차 천일 결사 6차 백일 기도 정진 1일째</title>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;수행일지&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;몸이 피곤합니다. 몸이 피곤하니 정신도 멍한 상태입니다. 이익을 따지니 자꾸 맘쓰는것이 옹졸해집니다. 일리를 가자하면 십리를 가주겠다는 마음으로 살아보아야겠습니다. 옹졸하니 자꾸 걸리는것이 많고 걸리는것이 많으니 삶이 피곤해지는것 같습니다. 맘이 편안한 삶이 결코 쉽지 않은것 같습니다. 감사합니다. 오늘 하루도 이왕이면 재미있고 즐겁게 보내야겠습니다!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/05/8_6_1.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/05/8_6_1.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/05/8_6_1.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 21:19:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>8차 천일 결사 5차 백일 기도 정진 100일째</title>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;수행일지&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;어제 똥을 선물 받았습니다. 그리고 그 똥을 움켜쥐고는 어쩔줄 몰라했습니다. 그 똥을 선물한 상대를 미워하고 원망했습니다. 그 똥에 사로잡혀 한참을 고통스러워했습니다. 상대가 똥을 선물한 자유가 있듯이 나는 그 선물을 받지 않을 자유도 있습니다. 그 선물을 받지 않으면 되는것을 그 선물을 받아들고서는 상대를 미워했습니다. 다 내가 선택한 괴로움입니다. 잠깐 미쳐서 상대를 미워했습니다. 참회합니다.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/04/8_5_100.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/04/8_5_100.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/04/8_5_100.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 21:21:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>8차 천일 결사 5차 백일 기도 정진 99일째</title>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;수행일지&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;네 생각에 사로잡혀 어제 하루를 허무하게 보냈습니다. 내가 하고자 한 일은 조금도 못하고 오로지 생각에 사로잡혀 하루종일 허우적대다가 소중한 일요일이 가버렸습니다. 마음에 아쉬움이 남습니다. 그 순간 알아차리고 놓아야 하는데 오늘 수행하면서 그나마 조금 알아차릴수 있었습니다. 어제는 어제고 오늘은 또 오늘일에 충실하며 다시 일어나 나의 길을 가야겠습니다. 지금 마음은 평온합니다. 감사합니다.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/03/8_5_99.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/03/8_5_99.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/03/8_5_99.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2015 21:15:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>8차 천일 결사 5차 백일 기도 정진 98일째</title>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;수행일지&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;마음에 두려움이 있습니다. 그래서 상대방의 말에 신경질적으로 반응했습니다. 그의 말을 지키지 못했을 경우에 대한 비난 또는 그것을 지키지 못한 못난 나라는 자책이 두려워서 끊임없이 나를 방어하고 상대방의 말에 화난 어조로 답했습니다. 미래의 어떤 일을 가정하고 아직 일어나지도 않은 일을 가지고 싸우고 있었습니다. 지금까지 무섭고 두려웠나 봅니다. 상대방의 말에 신경질적으로 반응하는것은 두려움 때문이었습니다. 나의 무의식에는 아주 오랫동안 두려움이 있었나봅니다. 오늘 하루도 저에 관해서 하나씩 알아가는 하루입니다. 감사합니다!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/02/8_5_98.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/02/8_5_98.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/02/8_5_98.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2015 21:17:46 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>8차 천일 결사 5차 백일 기도 정진 97일째</title>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;수행일지&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;상대방의 말을 너무 지키려는 경향이 있습니다. 상대방이 무슨말을하면 어떻게 해서든지 그 말을 지키기 위해서 신경을 씁니다. 그러다보니 상대방의 말에 너무 민감하게 반응하게 됩니다. 상대방의 말이 스트레스로 다가옵니다. 그의 말은 단지 그의 의견일 뿐입니다. 내가 그의 말에 따라야 할 이유는 어디에도 없습니다. 해줄수 있으면 좋고 못하면 «죄송합니다» 이렇게 가볍게 받아 들여야겠습니다. 나의 무의식에는 이런 습이 있었나 봅니다. 이렇게 알 수 있어 감사합니다. 이 습이 나올때마다 알아차리는 연습을 해 보아야겠습니다. 감사합니다. 오늘도 즐거운 하루 입니다.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/01/8_5_97.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/01/8_5_97.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/01/8_5_97.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2015 00:43:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>8차 천일 결사 5차 백일 기도 정진 96일째</title>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;수행일지&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;명상중 아직 호흡에 집중이 잘 되지 않습니다. 하지만 가볍게 받아들이니 않되면 다시 가볍게 호흡으로 돌아올 수 있습니다. 않되는것을 무겁게 받아들이면 다시 하기 힘든것 갈습니다. 않되는 나를 자꾸 탓하게 됩니다. 하지만 가볍게하니 않되면 다시 하는것이 부담스럽지 않습니다. 않되면 다시 하기를 수없이 반복합니다. 그 반복속에 길이 있습니다. 않되면 될때까지 수없이 반복해보리라 다짐하니 마음이 단단해지는 느낌입니다. 어제도 잘 살았으니 오늘도 잘 살것입니다. 감사합니다.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/07/31/8_5_96.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/07/31/8_5_96.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/07/31/8_5_96.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 21:17:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
