<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>[Young Gyu's blog]</title>
        <description>Young Gyu Park Story, Tech and Life</description>
        <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/</link>
        <language>ko</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 12:45:49 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 19:40:38 GMT</pubDate>
        <ttl>180</ttl>
        <atom:link href="http://ygpark2.github.io/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

        
        <item>
            <title>Some people think that all university students should study whatever they like. Others believe that they sholud only be allowed to study subjects that will be useful in the future, such as those related to science and technology.</title>
            <description>&lt;p id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;Q. Some people think that all university students should study whatever they like. Others believe that they sholud only be allowed to study subjects that will be useful in the future, such as those related to science and technology. Discuss both these views and give your own opinion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/22/ielts_writing_university_subjects/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/22/ielts_writing_university_subjects/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/22/ielts_writing_university_subjects/</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 19:40:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>It is important for children to learn the difference between right and wrong at an early age. Punishment is necessary to help them learn this distinction.</title>
            <description>&lt;p id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;Q. It is important for children to learn the difference between right and wrong at an early age. Punishment is necessary to help them learn this distinction. To what extent do you agree or disagree with this opinion? What sort of punishment should parents and teachers be allowed to use to teach good behaviour to children?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;Education has been always the main interest for parents. Especially, the way to enhance the children’s ability to discern what is right and what is wrong is very critical. Some people believe that punishment is the most effective way to teach about it. However, I am convinced that punishment is not the right way to teach children about developing moral judgment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;First of all, there is no scientific evidence to prove that punishment have not shown yet its effectieness as an educational tool. But it seems that many people still believe that punishment is a necessary to achieve the educational goal which help children to recognize what is socially acceptable behaviour and what is not.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/21/ielts_writing_punishment_for_education/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/21/ielts_writing_punishment_for_education/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/21/ielts_writing_punishment_for_education/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2015 15:57:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Some people believe that visitors to other countries should follow local customs and behaviour. Others disagree and think that the host country should welcome cultural differences.</title>
            <description>&lt;p id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;Q. Some people believe that visitors to other countries should follow local customs and behaviour. Others disagree and think that the host country should welcome cultural differences. Discuss both these views and give your opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;The view of cultural differences has been the controversial issue amongst people. Some people believe that visitors need to respect or abide by the local rules or tradition whereas other people believe that the country need to show more leniency to foreigners. I will contemplate both perspectives and add comment to the reasoned conclusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;Firstly, as many people travel abroad thanks to the technical advances in aviation industry leading to lower the cost of flying, they will frequently encounter some difficulties that resulted in the cultural difference in foreign countries where they are traveling. Obvioulsy the first impression they perceive in those countries will be embarrassment for most people in such cases. Thus the most effective way to minimize or ease the awkward circumstances is to learn the country, which you are about to travel, with regard to their culture and tradition in advance. Furthermore, it will help you to understand the country more deeply and enrich your traveling experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-4&#39;&gt;On the flip side, when it comes to the underdeveloped countries, foreign tourists are accounting for the main source of their income. In such cases, they seem to be more lenient for the visitors since their living need to heavily rely on the tourists’ expense. If you travel in those countries, you might encounter the unexpected hospitality from the local people who want your money. Thus I think the welcomeness the host country has shown is sometime resulted from the economic motivation rather than their pure mind to be friendly for the foreigners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-5&#39;&gt;In conclusion, there is no doubt that cultural differences are becomeing more crucial than ever before as our society is becomming globalized. Sometime we can be visitor to other countries and another time we can be a host for the foreign traveller. The most important thing we need to bear in mind is that we have to take the cultural difference for granted and embrace it since it is very natural part of our life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/15/ielts_writing_cultural_difference/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/15/ielts_writing_cultural_difference/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/15/ielts_writing_cultural_difference/</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 15:38:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Some people prefer to spend their lives doing the same things and avoiding change. Others, however, think that change is always a good thing.</title>
            <description>&lt;p id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;Q. Some people prefer to spend their lives doing the same things and avoiding change. Others, however, think that change is always a good thing. Discuss both these views and give your own opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;Most people struggle with change even if it is for the better, especially old people. Not all the changes were successful but we learned from the failures too. However, some people still believe any change will not be favorable to their life so that they strongly resist chnage. I will discuss both perspectives and add my thought on the matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;First of all, people who love to encounter change usually have had a number of good memories about change and these good memories are instensifying their favorable behaviour or decision toward change. For example, when I was an university student, IT technology was very popular and many expert predict that the IT jobs will be promising. On that account, I made up my mind to change my major from public adminitration to information communication technology and I am very content with the decision that I made at that time. This good consequence of the change seems to reinforce my action to positively react to change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-4&#39;&gt;On the other hand, it is very obvious that most people do not want to embrace change. The paramount reason for people to resist to the change is that they do not want to face uncertanities in which the change might bring. For instance, when they are compelled to adapt to the new technology in the company they are working, they will be highly likely to dislike the situation since they are not sure about how much they can perform in the new field. Basically, they are not happy with the uncertainty inherent the circumstances&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-5&#39;&gt;In conclusion, we can easily observe that there are two response patterns toward change. The first one is to welcome any change that they face since they have an accumulated positive experiences from many change they had. The other one is to resist change because they dislike the fear and anxiousness in which those change might bring. I personally believe that the change will bring more benefit in our life and we have thrived thank to the innovation in which the change result.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/11/chnage_and_avoiding/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/11/chnage_and_avoiding/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/11/chnage_and_avoiding/</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 22:13:06 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>The One and Only Reason to Customize IntelliJ IDEA Memory Settings</title>
            <description>&lt;p id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;http://tomaszdziurko.pl/2015/11/1-and-the-only-one-to-customize-intellij-idea-memory-settings/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;위의 글을 번역했습니다.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;인텔리제이 메모리 설정&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#39;p-4&#39;&gt;목표&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-5&#39;&gt;메모리 사용과 속도 개선을 위한 최적의 메모리 설정을 찾는 것입니다.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#39;p-6&#39;&gt;jstat -gcutil&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-7&#39;&gt;JDK에는 JVM과 Garbage Collector 통계를 모니터하기위한 툴입니다. 많은 옵션들이 있지만 우리는 여기서 다음의 옵션을 살펴보겠습니다.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-8&#39;&gt;-gcutil - Summary of garbage collection statistics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-9&#39;&gt;S0: Survivor space 0 utilization as a percentage of the space’s current capacity. S1: Survivor space 1 utilization as a percentage of the space’s current capacity. E: Eden space utilization as a percentage of the space’s current capacity. O: Old space utilization as a percentage of the space’s current capacity. M: Metaspace utilization as a percentage of the space’s current capacity. CCS: Compressed class space utilization as a percentage. YGC: Number of young generation GC events. YGCT: Young generation garbage collection time. FGC: Number of full GC events. FGCT: Full garbage collection time. GCT: Total garbage collection time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-10&#39;&gt;이 명령어의 출력 결과는 다음과 같습니다.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-11&#39;&gt;S0 S1 E O M CCS YGC YGCT FGC FGCT GCT 89.70 0.00 81.26 74.27 95.68 91.76 40 2.444 14 0.715 3.159&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-12&#39;&gt;이 글에서 가장 중요한 파라메터들은 GC 이벤트(YGC, GFC) 수이고 그리고 컬렉션 타임(YGCT, FGCT) 입니다.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 id=&#39;p-13&#39;&gt;기본 설정&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-14&#39;&gt;-Xms128m -Xmx750m -XX:MaxPermSize=350m -XX:ReservedCodeCacheSize=240m -XX:+UseCompressedOops&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 id=&#39;p-15&#39;&gt;대용량 설정(붉은색)&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-16&#39;&gt;-Xms2g -Xmx2g -XX:ReservedCodeCacheSize=1024m -XX:+UseCompressedOops -server -Xms2g -Xmx2g -XX:NewRatio=3 -Xss16m -XX:+UseConcMarkSweepGC -XX:+CMSParallelRemarkEnabled -XX:ConcGCThreads=4 -XX:MaxPermSize=350m -XX:ReservedCodeCacheSize=240m -XX:+AlwaysPreTouch -XX:+TieredCompilation -XX:+UseCompressedOops -XX:SoftRefLRUPolicyMSPerMB=50 -ea -Dsun.io.useCanonCaches=false -Djava.net.preferIPv4Stack=true -Djsse.enableSNIExtension=false -XX:+HeapDumpOnOutOfMemoryError -XX:-OmitStackTraceInFastThrow -Dawt.useSystemAAFontSettings=lcd ### 복잡한 설정(오렌지색)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-17&#39;&gt;-server -Xms2g -Xmx2g -XX:NewRatio=3 -Xss16m -XX:+UseConcMarkSweepGC -XX:+CMSParallelRemarkEnabled -XX:ConcGCThreads=4 -XX:ReservedCodeCacheSize=240m -XX:+AlwaysPreTouch -XX:+TieredCompilation -XX:+UseCompressedOops -XX:SoftRefLRUPolicyMSPerMB=50 -Dsun.io.useCanonCaches=false -Djava.net.preferIPv4Stack=true -Djsse.enableSNIExtension=false -ea&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-18&#39;&gt;이 설정값들은 bin 폴더안의 idea64.vmoptions파일에 있습니다.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 id=&#39;p-19&#39;&gt;실험결과&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-20&#39;&gt;생략합니다.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#39;p-21&#39;&gt;요약&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-22&#39;&gt;인텔리제이 메모리 설정을 조그만 바꿈으로서 아주 상당한 성능의 개선을 볼수있다. 물론 더 많은 메모리를 할당할수록 더 많은 성능의 개선을 기대할 수 있다. 하지만 우리는 메모리를 사용하는 많은 프로그램들과 함께 사용해야하므로 성능과 메모리 소비에서 최적의 설정값들을 찾는것이 이 글의 목적이다. 대부분의 경우에는 Xmx값을 2g 또는 3g 사이에서 설정할 경우 가장 최상의 성능을 기대할 수 있는것 같다. 만약 당신이 좀 더 여유 시간이 있으시다면 jstat 또는 jvisualm가지고 여러 VM flags값들을 설정하면서 최고의 성능을 낼 수 있는 설정을 찾으면 좋을것같다.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-23&#39;&gt;이글을 읽고 찾은 나의 설정 값&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-24&#39;&gt;-server -Xms2g -Xmx2g -XX:NewRatio=3 -Xss16m -XX:+UseConcMarkSweepGC -XX:+CMSParallelRemarkEnabled -XX:ConcGCThreads=4 -XX:MaxPermSize=350m -XX:ReservedCodeCacheSize=240m -XX:+AlwaysPreTouch -XX:+TieredCompilation -XX:+UseCompressedOops -XX:SoftRefLRUPolicyMSPerMB=50 -ea -Dsun.io.useCanonCaches=false -Djava.net.preferIPv4Stack=true -Djsse.enableSNIExtension=false -XX:+HeapDumpOnOutOfMemoryError -XX:-OmitStackTraceInFastThrow -Dawt.useSystemAAFontSettings=lcd&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/08/IntelliJ_IDEA_Memory_Settings/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/08/IntelliJ_IDEA_Memory_Settings/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/08/IntelliJ_IDEA_Memory_Settings/</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 16:15:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Several languages are in danger of extinction because they are spoken by very small numbers of people. Some people say that governments should spend public money on saving these languages, while others believe that would be a waste of money.</title>
            <description>&lt;p id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;Q.Several languages are in danger of extinction because they are spoken by very small numbers of people. Some people say that governments should spend public money on saving these languages, while others believe that would be a waste of money. Discuss both these views and give your opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;As the world is becomming smaller thanks to globalization, people have a tendency to use only the languages which can be communicated globaly. Some people believe that a government’s intervention to deter the phenomenon of the disapearing languages is necessarily whereas other people argue that we can do many important matters which is much more crucial than the prevention of languages’ extinction. I believe that the goverment have to invest public money to develop polocies to protect the disappearance of languages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;First of all, the argument that the goverment’s effort to save the languages spoken by minorities is wasteful do not make sense as the language is the most prominent invention human being developed. Supposing that we do not have such a minor language, basically we are denying and destroying every legacy the people of speaking the language developed. It is quite lamentable that the goverment do not take any action to preserve the minor languages which enrich our cultural variety and provide some precious knowledge to our next genrations to come.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-4&#39;&gt;On the other hand, basically the money we collected from people under the name of tax is supposed to spend for enhancing the public welfare. I cannot find any other option except the spent money for preserving the languagates in dager of disappearing since this will definately flourish our culture and extend our capacity of taking care of minorities eventually. Thus I strongly support the idea that we should persist the effort to preserve the disapearing languages and reach a consensus with regard to investing money on prevention of languages extinction since the money is based on tax payer’s money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-5&#39;&gt;In summary, I believe the goverment need to take this issue seriously and raise public awareness about this issue so that more people can pay attention to this issue. As the public interests are growing rapidly, the solution for the problem of preserving the disapearing languages will be easily found or the task to achieve the goal will be relatively easier.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/03/languages_extinction/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/03/languages_extinction/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/03/languages_extinction/</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 00:12:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Some people think that museums should be enjoyable places to entertain people, while others believe that the purpose of museums is to educate.</title>
            <description>&lt;p id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;Q. Some people think that museums should be enjoyable places to entertain people, while others believe that the purpose of museums is to educate. Discuss both views and give your own opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;The purpose of museums has been quite controversial since the understanding of the purpose is sharply contrast amongst people. Some people believe that we need to fortify the role of education in museum whereas other people think that the entertainment purpose should be prioritized admong other roles. In this essay, I want to weigh the both views and add my thought about the issue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;It is widely considered that the paramount role of museum is to provide a variety of information about our ancestor to people as well as to record our present generation’s thought and living style in order to give a lesson to our next generation to come. This is the main reason why many schools harness the museum as a place to teach students. However, if we put too much stress on the role of education in museum, people will be easily losing their interesting, which come to the place where most people is very not keen to go very frequently. Thus I believe we need to come up with measures to encourage the students to learn many lessons or obtain valuable information without compromising their interest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-4&#39;&gt;On the other hand, there is very strong tendency to utilize musuems as a place to hold many cultural performance events as the museum is quite suitable place to serve that purpose. As this kind of events are increasing, people often apt to forget why they come to the museum and only focus on the enjoyment the events give. I do not oppose the function of museum to give pleasure people through various mediums. However, if we lose the main purpose the museum, which is education, by mesmerizing those pleasures. we are actully denying the original reason for the existence of the museum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-5&#39;&gt;In summary, museum is able to server a variety of purposes as long as it is faithfully serving the original role to educate people and preserve the legacy. Therefore, we need to be vigilant in order not to confuse the original functionalities of museum.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/02/purpose_of_museum/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/02/purpose_of_museum/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/12/02/purpose_of_museum/</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 22:24:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Explain some of the ways in which human are damaging the environment.</title>
            <description>&lt;p id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;Q. Explain some of the ways in which human are damaging the environment. What can governments do to address these problems? What can individual people do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;Environment has been with us before human being appeared on the earth. we cannot live without the environment and the quality of life is heavily affected by the state of environment. I want to discuss about what we can do this important environment in terms of the perspective of governments and individual people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;Human beings are the main responsible for the current environmental problems such as global warming, smog and&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-4&#39;&gt;From the government point of view, the most imminent task for the government to do is to tighten the regulation imposed on the companies which produce tremendous amount of pollution. These companies are quite frequently caught due to the damage on the environment they incur. However, the penalty or punishment seems not strict enough to deter the recurrence of the violation the company committed. Thus we need to strengthen the punishment for any environmental violation as well as apply heavy punishment for the company which made the same crime again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-5&#39;&gt;From the individual point of view,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/11/26/human_damaging_environment/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/11/26/human_damaging_environment/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/11/26/human_damaging_environment/</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 15:30:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Universities should accept equal numbers of male and female students in every subject.</title>
            <description>&lt;p id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;Q. Universities should accept equal numbers of male and female students in every subject. To what extent do you agree or disagree?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;Some people believe that there should be no difference in the number of students in every subject regardless of their sexuality. However I personally believe if we focus on the equality of sex too much, we might have to sacrifice some the of values that we want to achieve through university education. I will highlight the values we can obtain in favor of the gender inequality in university.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;Firstly, assuming that universities are obliged to accept people in equal proportion between men and women irrespective of their ability or competitiveness with regard to study, we might punish the people who are more competitive people because of gender equality. For example, a person who had a very high academic capability might have to give up the chance to develop his or her career to conduct further study in higher education. The less capable person in study will gain an admission from university thanks to the consideration to allocate equal ratio between men and women, which ultimately lead to making our education system worser and demotivating smart people to study in university.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-4&#39;&gt;Secondly, we have many universities allowed to give a chance for female only to study in Korea. If the argument that universities should consider the students’ gender in selecting students is justified, we are basically denying the justification of those universities’ existence since they fail to meet the very important requirement to accept equal gender ratio of students. However, those universities are showing a good academic achievement in teaching students and research a subject with only female students. From this case, we can see there is no corelation between the same number of men and women students and the consideration of gender equality in university will undermine the competitiveness of university.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-5&#39;&gt;In conclusion, I am strongly convinced that we should abolish any constraints to restrict the admission of university because of their gender. If we not take any action to prevent this absurd regulation, we might have to face a disaster that people start to disregard the university and nobody want to pursue a study in higher education system.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/11/24/university_equal_admission/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/11/24/university_equal_admission/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/11/24/university_equal_admission/</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2015 16:28:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>오일러 프로젝트 haskell solutions</title>
            <description>&lt;h4 id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;Problem 45&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;Triangle, pentagonal, and hexagonal numbers are generated by the following formulae:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;Triangle Tn=n(n+1)/2 1, 3, 6, 10, 15, … Pentagonal Pn=n(3n−1)/2 1, 5, 12, 22, 35, … Hexagonal Hn=n(2n−1) 1, 6, 15, 28, 45, …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-4&#39;&gt;It can be verified that T285 = P165 = H143 = 40755.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-5&#39;&gt;Find the next triangle number that is also pentagonal and hexagonal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 id=&#39;p-6&#39;&gt;Solution&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-7&#39;&gt;import Data.List&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-8&#39;&gt;let t x = x&lt;em&gt;(x+1)/2 let p x = x&lt;/em&gt;(3&lt;em&gt;x-1)/2 let h x = x&lt;/em&gt;(2*x-1)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-9&#39;&gt;filter (-&amp;gt; p(x) &lt;code&gt;elemIndex&lt;/code&gt; [t x | x &amp;lt;- [1..500]] /= Nothing) [1..500]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 id=&#39;p-10&#39;&gt;Problem 46&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-11&#39;&gt;It was proposed by Christian Goldbach that every odd composite number can be written as the sum of a prime and twice a square.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-12&#39;&gt;9 = 7 + 2×1^2 15 = 7 + 2×2^2 21 = 3 + 2×3^2 25 = 7 + 2×3^2 27 = 19 + 2×2^2 33 = 31 + 2×1^2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-13&#39;&gt;It turns out that the conjecture was false.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-14&#39;&gt;What is the smallest odd composite that cannot be written as the sum of a prime and twice a square?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 id=&#39;p-15&#39;&gt;Solution&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-16&#39;&gt;import Data.List.Split – splitOn&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-17&#39;&gt;let square x y = map (-&amp;gt; x + 2^z) [1..y]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-18&#39;&gt;map (-&amp;gt; square x) $ filter isPrime [1..100]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-19&#39;&gt;map (&lt;code&gt;div&lt;/code&gt; 2) $ map (21-) $ filter isPrime [1..21]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-20&#39;&gt;[sqrt(fromIntegral(25-x)/2) | x &amp;lt;- [1..25], isPrime x]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-21&#39;&gt;filter (-&amp;gt; last(splitOn «.» x) == «0») [show(sqrt(fromIntegral(25-x)/2)) | x &amp;lt;- [1..25], isPrime x]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-22&#39;&gt;let validateOdd z = filter (-&amp;gt; last(splitOn «.» x) == «0») [show(sqrt(fromIntegral(z-x)/2)) | x &amp;lt;- [1..z], isPrime x]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-23&#39;&gt;filter (-&amp;gt; length(validateOdd(x)) == 0) [x | x &amp;lt;- [1..10000], (not . isPrime) x, odd x]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 id=&#39;p-24&#39;&gt;Problem 47&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-25&#39;&gt;The first two consecutive numbers to have two distinct prime factors are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-26&#39;&gt;14 = 2 × 7 15 = 3 × 5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-27&#39;&gt;The first three consecutive numbers to have three distinct prime factors are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-28&#39;&gt;644 = 2² × 7 × 23 645 = 3 × 5 × 43 646 = 2 × 17 × 19.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-29&#39;&gt;Find the first four consecutive integers to have four distinct prime factors. What is the first of these numbers?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 id=&#39;p-30&#39;&gt;Solution&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-31&#39;&gt;import Data.List.Split – chunksOf import Data.List.Grouping – splitEvery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-32&#39;&gt;let divisors x = 1:[ y | y &amp;lt;- [2..(x &lt;code&gt;div&lt;/code&gt; 2)], x &lt;code&gt;mod&lt;/code&gt; y == 0] ++ [x]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-33&#39;&gt;let isPrime x = divisors x == [1,x]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-34&#39;&gt;filter ( x -&amp;gt; (sum(x) - head(x) * 4) == 4) $ chunksOf 4 $ take 10000 [n | n &amp;lt;- [1..], (length $ filter isPrime $ divisors n) == 5]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-35&#39;&gt;filter ( x -&amp;gt; (sum(x) - head(x) * 4) == 4) $ chunksOf 4 [n | n &amp;lt;- [10000..100000], (length $ filter isPrime $ divisors n) == 5]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/11/23/euler_project_solutions/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/11/23/euler_project_solutions/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/11/23/euler_project_solutions/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 16:05:06 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
