<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>[Young Gyu's blog]</title>
        <description>Young Gyu Park Story, Tech and Life</description>
        <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/</link>
        <language>ko</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 10:54:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 01:53:08 GMT</pubDate>
        <ttl>180</ttl>
        <atom:link href="http://ygpark2.github.io/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

        
        <item>
            <title>Nowadays the way many people interact with each other has changed because of technology.</title>
            <description></description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/11/01/ielts_writing_interaction_technology/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/11/01/ielts_writing_interaction_technology/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/11/01/ielts_writing_interaction_technology/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 01:53:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>In some countries the average weight of people is increasing and their levels of health and fitness are decreasing</title>
            <description>&lt;p id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;Q. In some countries the average weight of people is increasing and their levels of health and fitness are decreasing. What do you think are the causes of these problems and what measures could be taken to solve them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;Many countries have struggled to tackle the issue caused by high health care cost for the people who are suffering due to obesity. In this essay I will analyse the causes about why this trend is worsening and what measures we can take to alleviate or eradicate the problems of deteriorated people’s health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;The foremost reason for obesity is food. Especially, instant food is regarded as the main causes to aggravate the health of people. Owing to the convenience and the relatively cheap price of the instant food, people is inclined to eat quite frequently , which result in obesity related disease. Another reason might be the intake of too much sugar. A recent report analysing the amount of sugar people consume daily said that the level of people’s consumption is dangerous and suggested that the public health authority need to take prompt action to curb the trend otherwise the society will have to pay a tremendous amount of cost to manage diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-4&#39;&gt;One of the measures I can think of to deter the worsening health issue among people is to raise awareness of the severe consequence of failing to manage their health due to their reckless eating habit. Additionaly, building many fitness centers which are adjacent to people’s resident area will naturally lead to increase the likelihood of exercise. These methods will bring some meaningful change to the current tendency to improve the continously increasing the average weight of people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-5&#39;&gt;In summary, the reasons that I mentioned above are needed to be taken into further consideration to improve the problems of aggravating health and suggested measures should be implemented without hesitation to achieve the goal of maintaing people’s sound body.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/26/ielts_writing_traffic_pollution.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/26/ielts_writing_traffic_pollution.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/26/ielts_writing_traffic_pollution.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 00:47:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Increasing the price of petrol is the best way to solve growing traffic and pollution problems</title>
            <description>&lt;p id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;Q. Increasing the price of petrol is the best way to solve growing traffic and pollution problems. To what extent do you agree or disagree? What other measures do you think might be effective?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;Global warming and traffic jam, we are facing in our daily life, has received notable attention from many countries, which is believed to be caused by the sharply increasing the number of car on roads. Many people believe the price level of petrol is very cheap, which it stimulate people to buy more car. However I do not believe the petrol price is the only reason to aggravate the problems. I will examine what other measures can be considered to prevent the escalating pollution and traffic jam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;First of all, no one can deny that there is a close correlation between the price level of petrol and the escalating traffic jam and worsening pollution. However, it is quite naive belief that we are able to curb the number of cars and the pollution by solely controlling the price of petrol. Some of the people who are rich enough do not really care the price of petrol. Therefore I cannot trust such belief the price level of petrol will decisively determine the impact of traffic and pollution issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-4&#39;&gt;Secondly, the other measures to tackle those issues except setting the price of petrol are to levy a high tax on the buyer of the cars and to apply high tax rate to petrol. The money collected from the buyer under the name of tax should be invested to build new roads to lessen the traffic jam and to eliminate the bottleneck. In addition to this, the company to develop the equipment to clean the polluted air should be given incentives in terms of funding for research and development. Thus these methods will contribute significantly to contain the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-5&#39;&gt;In conclusion, as I examine the limited impact of price control for petrol against traffic and polution problems, we cannot solve the issues by only relying on the high price of petrol. Therefore we have to find a combined strategy to tackle the problems effectively and enhance the quality of human life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/26/ielts_writing_people_weight_problem.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/26/ielts_writing_people_weight_problem.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/26/ielts_writing_people_weight_problem.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 00:41:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Many people believe that social networking sites ( such as Facebook) have had a huge negative impact on both individuals and society. To what extend do you agree?</title>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;Many people believe that social networking sites ( such as Facebook) have had a huge negative impact on both individuals and society. To what extend do you agree?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;The vast majority of people are convinced that the increasing number of social networking sites seems to have side effect on people as well as society in terms of a variety of aspect. However, there are a few people still believe that the online networking application have encourage people to meet a new person and facilitated the connection between people. My argument about this issue is that we need to maximize the benefits such sites can bring about and minimize the negative effects they might incur.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;The first good point we can obtain in using those sites is that they actually make it easier to meet an unknown person. To elaborate more, as the society is more specialized, people are experiencing meeting new people within their speciality boundary. For example we have to spend most of our time in our workplace, it is quite hard to imagine that we ᅟare highly like to meet new people who are totally unrelated with our job. Thus, at these days, the sites are the only channel we can utilize to broaden our social relationship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-4&#39;&gt;Another positive aspect of harnessing those sites is that especially the society which is suffering due to low birth rate might be able to overcome the issue easily through those sites. For instance, as more people take advantage ot the sites, the number of marriage couple will naturally increase thanks to the sites, which will eventually lead to the high birth rate. Therefore the society need to make an effort to raise an awareness of those sites and encourage them to use more frequently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-5&#39;&gt;In conclusion, we can conclude that the social networking sites seems to be beneficially not only to our society but also to individuals&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/23/ielt_writing_social_networking.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/23/ielt_writing_social_networking.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/23/ielt_writing_social_networking.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 14:38:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Some people believe that unpaid community service should be a compulsory part of high school programms</title>
            <description>&lt;p id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;Some people believe that unpaid community service should be a compulsory part of high school programms (for example working for a charity, improving the neighbourhood or teaching sports to younger children) What extent do you agree or disagree?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;Some of the essential services in our community will not work properly without volunteers’ dedicated effort. I believe such volunteers have been educated about how important their works are and experienced how much pleasure they will receive in return for their work. Thus I totally agree with the idea to include the social service program to high school curriculum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;Firstly, we need to dwell on the several benefits from enforcing the course to ask the high school students to do social service without any financial compensation. The first thing they can obtain from the compelling social course is that they can fully enjoy the happyness money cannot give. For instance, one of my friends who had a strong idea to&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/21/ielt_writing_unpaid_community_service.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/21/ielt_writing_unpaid_community_service.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/21/ielt_writing_unpaid_community_service.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 12:19:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Art is considered an important part of a society as well as an expressio nof its culture. Do you think it is important for children to be taught art? Do you think children should be encouraged to focus an art rather than other subjects?</title>
            <description>&lt;p id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;Art has been essential element of any human society from prehistoric times. However, at these days, the unprecedented technology development seems to undermine the value of art in human growth. I personally believe that art seems to be undervalued that is should deserve and we need to find a way to promote to the education of art in our public school.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;First of all, as the increasing importance of creativity in many areas is receiving more attention, people tend to pay more attention to how to enhance their creativity. The most effective method to develop creativity has been the education of art since we can easily find the most creative person among the artists. In addition to this, art can also be used to cure a person who are psychologically damaged. Therefore, we can expect the benefits in terms of psychological aspect as well as develping creativity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;Even though the critical importance of art has been recoginized by an increasing number of people, the recognition with regard to art in our education system seems to be out of tune with public concerns. A big portion of our time in schools has been dedicated to teach other subjects by neglecting to spend more time to teach art. Furthermore, the exam to determine their ability to study in university to not include art subject, which eventually discourage students to study art.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-4&#39;&gt;In conclusion, we are living in the society or the education system that make little account of art subject. However, we have to build up a strong art education to foster more creative person.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/18/ielt_writing_art_education.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/18/ielt_writing_art_education.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/18/ielt_writing_art_education.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2015 23:42:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Some experts believe that it is better for children to begin learning a foreign language at primary school rather than secondary school Do you think advantages of this outweigh the disadvantages?</title>
            <description>&lt;p id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;The importance of learning a foreign language is increasing, as the globalizatio nis expedited in many countries. In this trend, some language master argue that foreign language education should be taught at primary school in stead of secondary school to maximize the effectiveness of the education of language learning. However, I believe that secondary school is the best time to teach foreign language because we can expect more benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;The first advantage of teaching foreign language at secondary school is that the students can easily understand the meaning of foreign word thanks to their concrete and abundant mother tongue’s vocabulary. If you teach foreign language to a primary student who is not fully developed his or her navive language, it will be extremly hard because he or she cannot understand a new foreign word which he or she never learnt the corresponding word in his or her mother tongue. In addition to this, adding new language to their premature mother tongue will not only deter the development of their mother tongue but also be not helpful to learn a foreign language beased on their fragile mother tongue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;On contrary, if we teach a foreign language from elementary school, we can easily find many drawbacks. The first thing among them is that to teach foreign language to elementary studentswill be not only hard but not useful since it will be extremely difficult to motivate students who are still having trouble to understand their own language. Secondary, the early starting of teaching foreign language will destroy their interest as to foreign language, which will lead people to the stage of abandoning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-4&#39;&gt;To sum up, the disadvantages we expect from the teaching foreign language in elementary school seems to outweigh the advantages we can obtain from secondary school.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/18/ielt_writing_forein_langugage.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/18/ielt_writing_forein_langugage.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/18/ielt_writing_forein_langugage.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2015 22:08:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>hakyll 설치법</title>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;lessc dependencies installation&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;npm install less-plugin-clean-css npm install lodash npm install commander npm install gear npm install del npm install gear-lib&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-3&#39;&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-4&#39;&gt;새글 파일 생성&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-5&#39;&gt;./jake &#39;doc:post[파일명, 제목]&#39;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-6&#39;&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/17/hakyll_installation.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/17/hakyll_installation.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/10/17/hakyll_installation.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 15:01:41 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>8차 천일 결사 6차 백일 기도 정진 1일째</title>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;수행일지&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;몸이 피곤합니다. 몸이 피곤하니 정신도 멍한 상태입니다. 이익을 따지니 자꾸 맘쓰는것이 옹졸해집니다. 일리를 가자하면 십리를 가주겠다는 마음으로 살아보아야겠습니다. 옹졸하니 자꾸 걸리는것이 많고 걸리는것이 많으니 삶이 피곤해지는것 같습니다. 맘이 편안한 삶이 결코 쉽지 않은것 같습니다. 감사합니다. 오늘 하루도 이왕이면 재미있고 즐겁게 보내야겠습니다!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/05/8_6_1.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/05/8_6_1.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/05/8_6_1.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 21:19:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>8차 천일 결사 5차 백일 기도 정진 100일째</title>
            <description>&lt;h2 id=&#39;p-1&#39;&gt;수행일지&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id=&#39;p-2&#39;&gt;어제 똥을 선물 받았습니다. 그리고 그 똥을 움켜쥐고는 어쩔줄 몰라했습니다. 그 똥을 선물한 상대를 미워하고 원망했습니다. 그 똥에 사로잡혀 한참을 고통스러워했습니다. 상대가 똥을 선물한 자유가 있듯이 나는 그 선물을 받지 않을 자유도 있습니다. 그 선물을 받지 않으면 되는것을 그 선물을 받아들고서는 상대를 미워했습니다. 다 내가 선택한 괴로움입니다. 잠깐 미쳐서 상대를 미워했습니다. 참회합니다.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <link>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/04/8_5_100.html/</link>
            <comments>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/04/8_5_100.html/#disqus_thread</comments>
            <guid>http://ygpark2.github.io/posts/2015/08/04/8_5_100.html/</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 21:21:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
